//XML Tag Usage In HTML
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
  <title>Example Document</title>
  <summary>This is a summary of the document.</summary>
  <content>
    <section>
      <heading>Section 1</heading>
      <paragraph>This is the content of section 1.</paragraph>
    </section>
    <section>
      <heading>Section 2</heading>
      <paragraph>This is the content of section 2.</paragraph>
    </section>
  </content>
</root>

//XML Usage In Code Documentation

/// <summary> 
/// A summary of what the class/function does. 
/// </summary>

/// <see cref="Code"/>
/// This tag is used to create a reference to another code element, such as a class, method, or property. 
/// It allows you to create cross-references within the documentation.

/// <param name="param"> 
/// This tag is used to describe the parameters of a method or function. 
/// It typically includes the name of the parameter and provides a description of its purpose and expected usage. 
/// </param>

/// <return> 
/// This tag is used to describe the return value of a method or function. 
/// It provides information about the type of the returned value and its meaning or purpose. 
/// </return>

/// <returns> 
/// This tag is used to describe the return value of a method or function. 
/// It provides information about the type of the returned value and its meaning or purpose. 
/// </returns>

/// <example>
/// This tag is used to provide example code that demonstrates the usage of a particular code element. 
/// It is helpful for illustrating how to use a class, method, or property in practice.
/// </example>

/// <exception> 
///  This tag is used to document the exceptions that a method or function may throw. 
///  It includes information about the type of exception and provides a description of when and why the exception may be thrown.
/// </exception>

/// <remarks>
/// This tag is used to provide additional remarks or information about a code element that may not fit into other tags. 
/// It can be used to explain implementation details, provide additional context, or offer general advice.
/// </remarks>
 
